<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="heroes.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<heroes source="Marvel">
    <description>
    El Universo cinematográfico de Marvel es una franquicia de medios y un universo compartido, centrada
    en una serie de películas de superhéroes producidas independientemente por Marvel Studios y basadas en
    los personajes que aparecen en las publicaciones de Marvel Comics.
    </description>
    <hero id="1009664">
        <name>Thor</name>
        <description>As the Norse God of thunder and lightning, Thor wields one of the greatest weapons ever made, the enchanted hammer Mjolnir. While others have described Thor as an over-muscled, oafish imbecile, he's quite smart and compassionate.  He's self-assured, and he would never, ever stop fighting for a worthwhile cause.</description>
        <image>http://i.annihil.us/u/prod/marvel/i/mg/d/d0/5269657a74350/standard_fantastic.jpg</image>
        <urldetail>http://marvel.com/characters/1009664/thor/featured?utm_campaign=apiRef&amp;utm_source=e894ad1f6af082d2b6b7a63ff20f35e0</urldetail>
    </hero>

    <hero id="1009282">
        <name>Doctor Strange</name>
        <description>Once a highly successful, yet notably egotistical, surgeon, Doctor Stephen Strange endured a terrible accident that led him to evolve in ways he could have never foreseen.</description>
        <image>http://i.annihil.us/u/prod/marvel/i/mg/5/f0/5261a85a501fe/standard_fantastic.jpg</image>
        <urldetail>http://marvel.com/comics/characters/1009282/doctor_strange?utm_campaign=apiRef&amp;utm_source=e894ad1f6af082d2b6b7a63ff20f35e0</urldetail>
    </hero>
    <hero id="1009351">
        <name>Hulk</name>
        <description>Caught in a gamma bomb explosion while trying to save the life of a teenager, Dr. Bruce Banner was transformed into the incredibly powerful creature called the Hulk. An all too often misunderstood hero, the angrier the Hulk gets, the stronger the Hulk gets.</description>
        <image>http://i.annihil.us/u/prod/marvel/i/mg/5/a0/538615ca33ab0/standard_fantastic.jpg</image>
        <urldetail>http://marvel.com/comics/characters/1009351/hulk?utm_campaign=apiRef&amp;utm_source=e894ad1f6af082d2b6b7a63ff20f35e0</urldetail>
    </hero>

    <hero id="1009610">
        <name>Spider-Man</name>
        <description>Bitten by a radioactive spider, high school student Peter Parker gained the speed, strength and powers of a spider. Adopting the name Spider-Man, Peter hoped to start a career using his new abilities. Taught that with great power comes great responsibility, Spidey has vowed to use his powers to help people.</description>
        <image>http://i.annihil.us/u/prod/marvel/i/mg/3/50/526548a343e4b/standard_fantastic.jpg</image>
        <urldetail>http://marvel.com/comics/characters/1009610/spider-man?utm_campaign=apiRef&amp;utm_source=e894ad1f6af082d2b6b7a63ff20f35e0</urldetail>
    </hero>

    <hero id="1009368">
        <name>Iron Man</name>
        <description>Wounded, captured and forced to build a weapon by his enemies, billionaire industrialist Tony Stark instead created an advanced suit of armor to save his life and escape captivity. Now with a new outlook on life, Tony uses his money and intelligence to make the world a safer, better place as Iron Man.</description>
        <image>http://i.annihil.us/u/prod/marvel/i/mg/9/c0/527bb7b37ff55/standard_fantastic.jpg</image>
        <urldetail>http://marvel.com/comics/characters/1009368/iron_man?utm_campaign=apiRef&amp;utm_source=e894ad1f6af082d2b6b7a63ff20f35e0</urldetail>
    </hero>

    <hero id="1009220">
        <name>Captain America</name>
        <description>Vowing to serve his country any way he could, young Steve Rogers took the super soldier serum to become America's one-man army. Fighting for the red, white and blue for over 60 years, Captain America is the living, breathing symbol of freedom and liberty.</description>
        <image>http://i.annihil.us/u/prod/marvel/i/mg/3/50/537ba56d31087/standard_fantastic.jpg</image>
        <urldetail>http://marvel.com/comics/characters/1009220/captain_america?utm_campaign=apiRef&amp;utm_source=e894ad1f6af082d2b6b7a63ff20f35e0</urldetail>
    </hero>

    <hero id="1009189">
        <name>Black Widow</name>
        <description>Trusted by some and feared by most, the Black Widow strives to make up for the bad she had done in the past by helping the world, even if that means getting her hands dirty in the process.</description>
        <image>http://i.annihil.us/u/prod/marvel/i/mg/f/30/50fecad1f395b/standard_fantastic.jpg</image>
        <urldetail>http://marvel.com/comics/characters/1009189/black_widow?utm_campaign=apiRef&amp;utm_source=e894ad1f6af082d2b6b7a63ff20f35e0</urldetail>
    </hero>

    <hero id="1009187">
        <name>Black Panther</name>
        <description>As the king of the African nation of Wakanda, T’Challa protects his people as the latest in a legacy line of Black Panther warriors.</description>
        <image>http://i.annihil.us/u/prod/marvel/i/mg/6/60/5261a80a67e7d/standard_fantastic.jpg</image>
        <urldetail>http://marvel.com/comics/characters/1009187/black_panther?utm_campaign=apiRef&amp;utm_source=e894ad1f6af082d2b6b7a63ff20f35e0</urldetail>
    </hero>
    
</heroes>